<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<language id="33">
	<page id="4816301" title="DeadAir T Files" descr="names used in DeadAir Mods" voice="no">
		<!-- 3323247 == deadair -->
		<!--48163x69 == 3323247 since there is a character limit -->
		<!--48163##-->
		<t id="100">Empire de Amarr</t>
		<t id="101">L'Empire de Amarr est un patchwork tentaculaire de provinces de type féodal maintenues ensemble par la puissance de l'empereur. La religion a toujours joué un grand rôle dans la politique damarrienne et les Amarriens croient être les maîtres légitimes du monde, ce qui envenime leurs relations avec leurs voisins. Une autre source d'animosité de la part des autres empires est le fait que les Amarriens pratiquent l'esclavage.</t>
		<t id="102">DAM</t>
		<t id="103">Licence d'équipement de l'Empire</t>
		<t id="104">Licence de vaisseaux capitaux de l'Empire</t>
		<t id="105">Guerrier de l'Empire</t>
		<t id="106">Ami de l'Empire</t>
		<t id="107">Licence d'équipement à usage général de l'Empire</t>
		<t id="108">Licence de vaisseaux à usage général de l'Empire</t>
		<t id="109">Licence d'équipement militaire de l'Empire</t>
		<t id="110">Licence de vaisseaux militaire de l'Empire</t>
		<t id="111">Licence de police de l'Empire</t>
		<t id="112">Licence du module de construction de vaisseaux capitaux de l'Empire</t>
		<t id="113">Licence pour les modules auxiliaires de construction navale de l'Empire</t>
		<t id="114">Licence pour les modules avancés de l'Empire</t>
		<t id="115">Licence des modules de bases de l'Empire</t>
		<t id="116">Licence des modules intermédiaires de l'Empire</t>
		<t id="117">Abonnement à l'offre commerciale de l'Empire</t>
		<t id="118">L'Empire</t>
		<t id="119">Contrat de vente du navire de l'Empire</t>
		<t id="120">(T5ZI-S){20403,20}{20404,5}{20403,25}{20403,9}{20005,8004}{20403,19}</t>
		<t id="121">(N-8YET){20403,14}{20005,8004}{20404,8}{20403,25}{20403,5}{20403,20}</t>
		<t id="122">(MO-GZ5){20403,13}{20403,15}{20005,8004}{20403,7}{20403,25}{20404,5}</t>
		<t id="123">(1DQ1-A){20404,1}{20403,4}{20403,17}{20404,1}{20005,8004}{20403,1}</t>
		<t id="124">(8WA-Z6){20404,8}{20403,23}{20403,1}{20005,8004}{20403,26}{20404,6}</t>
		<t id="125">(5BTK-M){20404,5}{20403,2}{20403,20}{20403,11}{20005,8004}{20403,13}</t>
		<t id="126">(Y-OMTZ){20403,25}{20005,8004}{20403,15}{20403,13}{20403,20}{20403,25}</t>
		<t id="127">DA Noble Amarrien</t>
		<t id="128">DA Noble Amarrien \({20102,2011}\)</t>
		<t id="129">Vous êtes un jeune noble damarrien fatigué de votre vie confortable. Vous décidez de vous aventurer seul pour voir dans quel pétrin vous pouvez vous mettre.</t>
		<t id="130">(Y-MPWL){20403,25}{20005,8004}{20403,13}{20403,16}{20403,23}{20403,12}</t>
		<t id="131">xxx</t>
		<t id="132">xxx</t>
		<!-- Equipment -->
		<t id="200">{4816301,102}(DAM) {20111,5031}(L) Multifrequency Mega Beam Laser</t>
		<t id="201">Multifrequency</t>
		<t id="202">{4816301,102}(DAM) {20111,5031}(L) Radio Mega Beam Laser</t>
		<t id="203">Radio</t>
		<t id="204">{4816301,102}(DAM) {20111,5031}(L) Standard Mega Beam Laser</t>
		<t id="205">Standard</t>
		<t id="206">{4816301,102}(DAM) {20111,5021}(M) Multifrequency Heavy Beam Laser</t>
		<t id="207">{4816301,102}(DAM) {20111,5021}(M) Radio Heavy Beam Laser</t>
		<t id="208">{4816301,102}(DAM) {20111,5021}(M) Standard Heavy Beam Laser</t>
		<t id="209">{4816301,102}(DAM) {20111,5031}(L) Multifrequency Mega Beam Laser</t>
		<t id="210">{4816301,102}(DAM) {20111,5031}(L) Radio Mega Beam Laser</t>
		<t id="211">{4816301,102}(DAM) {20111,5031}(L) Standard Mega Beam Laser</t>
		<t id="212">{4816301,102}(DAM) {20111,3001}(XL) Judgement Electromagnetic Doomsday</t>
		<t id="280">{4816301,102}(DAM) {20111,5031}(L) {20107,3021}(All-round Engine)</t>
		<t id="290">Mega Beam Laser</t>
		<t id="291">Heavy Beam Laser</t>
		<!-- Weapon Description -->
		<t id="300">These energy based weapons do EM and Thermal damage, making these weapons great for cutting through shields, and not as good at penetrating armor. The multifrequency crystal attached randomly cycles the laser through the entire spectrum. The greatly increased damage comes at the cost of a significant reduction in range.</t>
		<t id="301">These energy based weapons do EM and Thermal damage, making these weapons great for cutting through shields, and not as good at penetrating armor. The radio crystal attached modulates the beam of a laser weapon into the radio frequencies. Offers greatly improved range but significantly lower damage.</t>
		<t id="302">These energy based weapons do EM and Thermal damage, making these weapons great for cutting through shields, and not as good at penetrating armor. The standard crystal attached modulates the beam of a laser weapon into the visible light spectrum.</t>
		<t id="303">The ultimate expression of God's Divine wrath, this weapon projects a beam of the Lord's holy light, designed to put sinners in their proper place.</t>
	</page>
</language>
